stockgraphicdesigns.com 2013-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Royalty Free Vector Packs | Photoshop Brushes Packs | StockGraphicDesigns

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com ](mailto:sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com).

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * If StockGraphicDesigns.com. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

_PayPal_

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

_Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider_

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

_Web beacons_

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of StockGraphicDesigns.com.. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

## Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com](mailto:sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com)

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

## Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. Displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

You can log in to our site using the sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect gives you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com ](mailto:sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com).

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

StockGraphicDesigns.com  
Kruthia Design Studio,  
9, Moorthy Nagar, College Road,  
Opp. to BSNL quarters, Tirupur, Tamilnadu  
India  
Email: [sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com](mailto:sales@stockgraphicdesigns.com)
